Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/anshuman-kumar-b2a47532 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

R

C++

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Hindi (Native or Bilingual)

Anshuman Kumar

Analytics and Machine learning

South West Delhi, Delhi, India

Summary

Experienced Application Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in ABAP, Databases, Big Data Analytics, Data Science, and Java. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Computer Software Engineering from Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University.

Experience

Accenture

Application Development Analyst December 2017 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Noida Area, India

Infogain

Intern

June 2016 - July 2016 (2 months)

Noida Area, India

Education

Guru Gobind Singh Indraprastha University
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Software
Engineering · (2013 - 2017)

New Era Public School - India 12th, PCM · (2010 - 2012)

New Era Public School - India 10th · (2004 - 2010)